O.W. Riegel Papers WLU.Coll.0387
Washington and Lee University, James G. Leyburn Library Special Collections and Archives
- Propaganda, 1912-1992; 12.58 Linear Feet 7 large storage boxes, 2 oversize boxes, and 3 other boxes (Box 1-16, Folder 1-466)
  - World War II, 1939-1945 (Box 2-4, Folder 75-279, Box 5-6, Box 1-5, Box 11, Oversize 1)
    - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 5-6, Box 1-5)
      This subseries containes unique items of the time period that distinguish it from other eras. Some interesting items of note include candy wrappers with U.S. army propaganda, an assortment of pro U.S. booklets in various languages, shoe lace packaging depicting the hanging of Hitler and Mossolini, and a hitler/Tojo pin cushion.
      - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 1)
      - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 2)
      - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 3)
      - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 4)
      - Ephemeral Materials, 1939-1945 (Box 5)
    - Oversize, 1939-1945 (Box 11)
    - Oversize, 1939-1945 (Box 15)
    - Booklets, 1941-1945 (Box 16)
  - Cold War, 1946-1992 (Box 7-8, Folder 280-400)
    Materials in this subseries relate to the Cold War era. Most items focus on communication from the U.S. to its citizens and foreign countries to gain support over Russia in the Cold War. Additionally, there are a few items from foreign nations aimed at U.S. audiences. Some items of note include some Russian Magazines, Chinese Magazines, and publications related to the United States Information Agency.
    Some items from this subseries have been separated from the main collection of materials and have been placed into the propaganda series oversize storage.
    - Correspondence, 1946-1992 (Box 7, Folder 280-286)
      This subseries consists of Riegel's correspondence related to the Cold War. It focuses mostly on specific events during the Cold War and the reach of government concerning foreign and domestic media and speech.
      - Ber-Bla, 1946-1992 (Folder 280)
      - Boo-Cha, 1946-1992 (Folder 281)
      - Che-Har, 1946-1992 (Folder 282)
      - Hol-Kip, 1946-1992 (Folder 283)
      - Lub-Sta, 1946-1992 (Folder 284)
      - Sti-Was, 1946-1992 (Folder 285)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1992 (Folder 286)
    - Foreign Publications, 1946-1992 (Box 7, Folder 287-298)
      This subseries consists of material made by foreign govenrments, mostly with the intent to reach an American audience. Some items of note include magazines from the Polish government, Russian Magazines, and a booklet about developing countries and the Soviet Bloc.
      - Foreign Publications, 1948-1949 (Folder 287)
      - Foreign Publications, 1950 (Folder 288)
      - Foreign Publications May-Oct., 1950 (Folder 289)
      - Foreign Publications, 1951 (Folder 290)
      - Foreign Publications, 1952 (Folder 291)
      - Foreign Publications, 1953 (Folder 292)
      - Foreign Publications Mar.-Apr., 1953 (Folder 293)
      - Foreign Publications Jul., 1953 (Folder 294)
      - Foreign Publications, 1953-1954 (Folder 295)
      - Foreign Publications, 1959-1962 (Folder 296)
      - Foreign Publications, 1962-1963 (Folder 297)
      - Foreign Publications, 1968 (Folder 298)
    - Government Publications, 1946-1992 (Box 7, Folder 299-332)
      This subseries focuses on material the U.S. and foreign governments produced for American citizens, often in the form of reports and booklets. Some items of note include a report on the U.S. international cultural program and "Telling America's Story Abroad" by the State Department.
      - Government Publications, 1946 (Folder 299)
      - Government Publications, 1946-1947 (Folder 300)
      - Government Publications, 1947 (Folder 301)
      - Government Publications, 1947-1948 (Folder 302)
      - Government Publications, 1948-1950 (Folder 303)
      - Government Publications, 1950 (Folder 304)
      - Government Publications, 1951 (Folder 305)
      - Government Publications Apr.-May, 1951 (Folder 306)
      - Government Publications, 1951-1952 (Folder 307)
      - Government Publications Jan.-May, 1952 (Folder 308)
      - Government Publications Jul., 1952 (Folder 309)
      - Government Publications Aug.-Oct., 1952 (Folder 310)
      - Government Publications, 1953 (Folder 311)
      - Government Publications, 1953-1954 (Folder 312)
      - Government Publications, 1954 (Folder 313)
      - Government Publications Mar.-Jun., 1954 (Folder 314)
      - Government Publications Apr.-Sep., 1954 (Folder 315)
      - Government Publications Sep.-Nov., 1954 (Folder 316)
      - Government Publications, 1954-1955 (Folder 317)
      - Government Publications Mar., 1955 (Folder 318)
      - Government Publications Apr.-Oct., 1955 (Folder 319)
      - Government Publications, 1956-1957 (Folder 320)
      - Government Publications Jan.-Mar., 1957 (Folder 321)
      - Government Publications, 1957-1958 (Folder 322)
      - Government Publications, 1959 (Folder 323)
      - Government Publications Jan.-Sep., 1960 (Folder 324)
      - Government Publications Sep., 1960 (Folder 325)
      - Government Publications, 1961-1963 (Folder 326)
      - Government Publications Jun., 1964 (Folder 327)
      - Government Publications, 1964-1965 (Folder 328)
      - Government Publications, 1965-1966 (Folder 329)
      - Government Publications, 1966-1975 (Folder 330)
      - Government Publications Miscellaneous, 1946-1975 (Folder 331)
      - Government Publications Miscellaneous, 1946-1975 (Folder 332)
    - Information Exchange, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 333)
    - Japan, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 334)
    - Newspapers, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 335-339)
      This subseries consists of a small assortment of clod war era newspapers hihglighting various events related to the cold war effort. Articles include international U.S. radio presence, the US information service's efforts, and international relations.
      - Newspapers, 1946-1949 (Folder 335)
      - Newspapers, 1949-1952 (Folder 336)
      - Newspapers, 1952-1958 (Folder 337)
      - Newspapers, 1963-1971 (Folder 338)
      - Newspapers Miscellaneous, 1946-1992 (Folder 339)
    - Photos, 1950-1952 (Box 8, Folder 340)
    - Press Releases, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 341-370)
      This subseries consists of press releases of events throughout the Cold War. These press releases come from several sources, most of them being from the U.S. Information Agency. There are also press releases from the Japan Detachment of Broadcasting and Visual Activities and the State Department.
      - Press Releases Feb.-Sep., 1947 (Folder 341)
      - Press Releases, 1948-1951 (Folder 342)
      - Press Releases, 1951-1954 (Folder 343)
      - Press Releases Mar. 4-15, 1954 (Folder 344)
      - Press Releases Mar.-Apr., 1954 (Folder 345)
      - Press Releases Apr.-May, 1954 (Folder 346)
      - Press Releases May-Jun., 1954 (Folder 347)
      - Press Releases Jun.-Jul., 1954 (Folder 348)
      - Press Releases Aug., 1954 (Folder 349)
      - Press Releases Sep., 1954 (Folder 350)
      - Press Releases Oct.-Nov., 1954 (Folder 351)
      - Press Releases Dec., 1954 (Folder 352)
      - Press Releases Jan.-Feb., 1955 (Folder 353)
      - Press Releases Mar., 1955 (Folder 354)
      - Press Releases Apr.-May, 1955 (Folder 355)
      - Press Releases Jun., 1955 (Folder 356)
      - Press Releases Jul., 1955 (Folder 357)
      - Press Releases Aug., 1955 (Folder 358)
      - Press Releases Sep., 1955 (Folder 359)
      - Press Releases Oct., 1955 (Folder 360)
      - Press Releases Nov.-Dec., 1955 (Folder 361)
      - Press Releases, 1956-1957 (Folder 362)
      - Press Releases, 1958-1961 (Folder 363)
      - Press Releases May 5-16, 1961 (Folder 364)
      - Press Releases May 17-25, 1961 (Folder 365)
      - Press Releases, 1961-1962 (Folder 366)
      - Press Releases, 1962-1967 (Folder 367)
      - Press Releases Feb.-Mar., 1977 (Folder 368)
      - Press Releases Mar.-Dec., 1977 (Folder 369)
      - Press Releases Miscellaneous, 1947-1977 (Folder 370)
    - Publications, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 371-383)
      This subseies contains publications from a variety of sources. Often in the form of booklets or magazines, topics vary, but most focus on the effects of propaganda and the Cold War. Some booklets of note include one on Germany's territorial shifts after the second World War, and a booklet on the efforts of Christian Trade Unions to combat the spread of Communism.
      - Publications, 1946-1950 (Folder 371)
      - Publications Jul., -1950 (Folder 372)
      - Publications, 1950-1952 (Folder 373)
      - Publications, 1952-1954 (Folder 374)
      - Publications, 1954 (Folder 375)
      - Publications, 1954-1955 (Folder 376)
      - Publications Sep.-Dec., 1955 (Folder 377)
      - Publications, 1955-1956 (Folder 378)
      - Publications Mar.-Jun., 1956 (Folder 379)
      - Publications, 1956-1957 (Folder 380)
      - Publications, 1957-1961 (Folder 381)
      - Publications, 1963-1980 (Folder 382)
      - Publications Miscellaneous, 1946-1992 (Folder 383)
    - Radio Scripts, 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 384-386)
      These radio scripts were intended to inform the American public in areas both related and unrelated to the Cold war. Script topics ranged from "The Secret of American Prosperity" to "Coronary Thrombosis".
      - Radio Scripts Oct. 7-10, 1955 (Folder 384)
      - Radio Scripts Oct. 10-11, 1955 (Folder 385)
      - Radio Scripts, 1955-1962 (Folder 386)
    - U.S.I.A., 1946-1992 (Box 8, Folder 387-398)
      The U.S. Information Agency sought to spread international awareness of U.S. values and culture to second and third world countries during the Cold War. Items in this subseries consist of programs, reports, briefings, newsletters, memorandums, and charts that conveyed how the agency operated internationally.
      - United States Information Agency, 1953 (Folder 387)
      - United States Information Agency, 1954 (Folder 388)
      - United States Information Agency, 1955 (Folder 389)
      - United States Information Agency, 1958-1960 (Folder 390)
      - United States Information Agency, 1961-1962 (Folder 391)
      - United States Information Agency, 1963-1964 (Folder 392)
      - United States Information Agency, 1964-1969 (Folder 393)
      - United States Information Agency, 1969-1970 (Folder 394)
      - United States Information Agency, 1970-1972 (Folder 395)
      - United States Information Agency, 1972-1977 (Folder 396)
      - United States Information Agency, 1953-1977 (Folder 397)
      - United States Information Agency, 1953-1977 (Folder 398)
      - United States Information Agency, 1953-1956 (Folder 398a)
    - US Propaganda, 1946-1958 (Box 8, Folder 399)
    - Miscellaneous, 1947-1966 (Box 8, Folder 400)
  - Korea, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 401-427)
    Items in this subseries relate to the Korean war, and mostly from an American perspective. Most of the items are propaganda leaflets, aiming to encourage Korean support of American troops. Some items of note include a booklet of alleged U.S. war crimes during the war, a booklet about war P.O.W.'s, and copies of anti-U.S. propaganda.
    - Alleged War Crimes, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Correspondence, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 402)
    - Leaflets, 1950-1961 (Box 9, Folder 404-421)
      Items in this subseries are strictly Korean war propaganda that was intended for Korean citizens. Nearly all items in this subseries are in Korean and have an english description or translation attached with the goals of what the propaganda was supposed to evoke from the reader.
      - Leaflets, 1951-1952 (Folder 404)
      - Leaflets May-Jul., 1952 (Folder 405)
      - Leaflets Jul.-Aug., 1952 (Folder 406)
      - Leaflets, 1952-1954 (Folder 407)
      - Leaflets, 1954-1955 (Folder 408)
      - Leaflets Jan.-Feb., 1955 (Folder 409)
      - Leaflets, 1955-1956 (Folder 410)
      - Leaflets, 1957 (Folder 411)
      - Leaflets Jan.-Feb., 1957 (Folder 412)
      - Leaflets Feb.-Apr., 1957 (Folder 413)
      - Leaflets Apr., 1957 (Folder 414)
      - Leaflets Apr.-Jul., 1957 (Folder 415)
      - Leaflets Jul.-Aug., 1957 (Folder 416)
      - Leaflets, 1957 (Folder 417)
      - Leaflets, 1957 (Folder 418)
      - Leaflets May, 1961 (Folder 419)
      - Leaflets May, 1961 (Folder 420)
      - Leaflets Miscellaneous, 1951-1961 (Folder 421)
    - Materials and Operations, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 422)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 423)
    - Photos, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 424)
    - Photos, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 425)
    - Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 426)
    - Miscellaneous, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 427)
    - Government Publications, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 403)
  - Vietnam, 1955-1975 (Box 9-10, Folder 428-461)
    Items in this subseries focus primarily on public opinion and propaganda related to the Vietnam war. Items of note include propaganda leaflets, notes by anti-war committees, letters written to government officials about the war, and petitions to end the war. Some items are stored separately due to their size. Some war posters and pro-Viet Cong banners are in oversize storage.
    - Committee on Vietnam, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 428-430)
      The Committee on Vietnam was a local organization in Lexington and Rockbridge County formed in opposition to the war effort. Riegel was a member of the Committee. This subseries consists of notes Riegel took of meetings and comments made by Committee members.
      - Committee on Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 428)
      - Committee on Vietnam, 1968 (Folder 429)
      - Committee on Vietnam, 1955-1975 (Folder 430)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 431-436)
      Riegel's correspondence related to the Vietnam war often focused on his hope in the ceasing of hostilities. Many letters are to congressmen, and other high ranking government officials. Included in this subseries are also a few letters from Riegel to President Johnson regarding the Vietnam War.
      - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Folder 431)
      - Correspondence Jan.-Jun., 1967 (Folder 432)
      - Correspondence, 1967-1970 (Folder 433)
      - Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Folder 434)
      - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Folder 435)
      - Correspondence, 1965-1972 (Folder 436)
    - Government Publications, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 437-443)
      The government publications regarding the Vietnam War in Riegel's papers focus on the nature of war propaganda and the status of combatant strategy and techniques as the war progressed.
      - Government Publications, 1963-1965 (Folder 437)
      - Government Publications, 1965-1966 (Folder 438)
      - Government Publications Mar., 1966 (Folder 439)
      - Government Publications Mar.-Apr., 1966 (Folder 440)
      - Government Publications May, 1966 (Folder 441)
      - Government Publications, 1966-1968 (Folder 442)
      - Government Publications Miscellanoeus, 1963-1968 (Folder 443)
    - Leaflets, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 444-450)
      The leaflets in this subseries are targeted towards a Vietnamese audience. Each leaflet has an english description or translation of its content, reasoning for its use, and the intended reaction that should be evoked by the reader. Larger items are not stored with this subseries, but rather in oversize storage, mainly consisting of posters and pro-Viet Cong war banners.
      - Leaflets, 1964-1968 (Folder 444)
      - Leaflets Jan.-Jun., 1969 (Folder 445)
      - Leaflets Jul.-Aug., 1969 (Folder 446)
      - Leaflets Sep.-Nov., 1969 (Folder 447)
      - Leaflets Nov., 1969 (Folder 448)
      - Leaflets Miscellanoeus, 1964-1969 (Folder 449)
      - Leaflets Miscellaneous, 1964-1969 (Folder 450)
    - Newspapers and Clippings, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 451)
    - Operations, 1955-1975 (Box 9, Folder 452-454)
      Items in this subseries consist of Riegel's notes about government events related to propaganda and public opinion in relation to the Vietnam War. These informal notes document events, such as National Liberation Front propaganda drives.
      - Operations, 1964-1972 (Folder 452)
      - Operations Miscellanoeus, 1960-1975 (Folder 453)
      - Operations Miscellaneous, 1960-1975 (Folder 454)
    - Press Releases, 1955-1975 (Box 10, Folder 455)
    - Publications, 1955-1975 (Box 10, Folder 456-459)
      Items in this subseries relate to published or disseminated to the public referencing the Vietnam War. Items of note include a petition to end the war, a voter's pledge to support anti-war candidates, and booklets and magazines related to the war effort.
      - Publications, 1965-1967 (Folder 456)
      - Publications, 1967-1969 (Folder 457)
      - Publications, 1969-1970 (Folder 458)
      - Publications Miscellaneous, 1965-1970 (Folder 459)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1975 (Box 10, Folder 460)
    - Miscellaneous, 1955-1975 (Box 10, Folder 461)
  - Propaganda Oversize, 1914-1992 (Box 12)
    Items in this subseries are the oversize materials coming from other parts of the Propaganda series. Within this subseries are magazines and posters from the Cold War and the Vietnam War. Additionally, there is a 1:15000 road map of Hannover, Germany.
  - Items to be Scanned, 1914-1993 (Box 13)
    Items in this subseries consist of government reports related to the office of war information. they have some damaged and require creating a scan to ensure further damage is prevented.
    This part of the collection requires restoration or preservation. Use of the collection is granted on a case by case basis. Please contact the Head of Special Collections at 540-458-8649 for more information.
  - Unprocessed Material, 1914-1993 (Box 13a)
    Items in this subseries have not yet been processed into the collection. Materials range from the Inter-War period to the Cold War.
- Public Opinion Quarterly, 1936-1970; Riegel, O. W. (Oscar Wetherhold); 1.1 Linear Feet (Box 1, Folder 1-84)
  This series consists of items related to Riegel's work with the Public Opinion Quarterly, an academic journal that focuses on forms of media and their effects on the public, primarily via Radio, the Press, and Movies. The bulk of material in this series consists of correspondence between Riegel, editors for the Public Opinion Quarterly, and prospective article writers.
  - Communications, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1-4)
    The Public Opinion Quarterly organized its articles into specific sections. Communications was one of those sections. Items in this subseries consist primarily of correspondence about articles that would fall under the communications section of the journal.
    - Ame-France, 1936-1970 (Folder 1)
    - Jon-Slo, 1936-1970 (Folder 2)
    - Articles, 1936-1970 (Folder 3)
    - Articles and Misc., 1936-1970 (Folder 4)
  - Controls, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 6-30)
    This subseries consists of general correspondence between Riegel and approximately 160 correspondents on various topics relating to the Public Opinion Quarterly (POQ). Subjects include anticipated articles for the POQ, Events affecting the POQ, and the POQ's structure.
    - Abb-Boe, 1936-1970 (Folder 6)
    - Book Review, 1936-1970 (Folder 7)
    - Bot-Cas, 1936-1970 (Folder 8)
    - Childs, 1936 (Folder 9)
    - Childs, 1937 (Folder 10)
    - Childs, 1938 (Folder 11)
    - Childs, 1939 (Folder 12)
    - Childs, 1940-1941 (Folder 13)
    - Childs, 1941-1943 (Folder 14)
    - M. Childs-Cor, 1936-1970 (Folder 15)
    - Dab-Dre, 1936-1970 (Folder 16)
    - Eth-Fos, 1936-1970 (Folder 17)
    - Free, 1939-1940 (Folder 18)
    - Free, 1940-1941 (Folder 19)
    - Freeman-Ham, 1936-1970 (Folder 20)
    - Hau-Kem, 1936-1970 (Folder 21)
    - Kip-Low, 1936-1970 (Folder 22)
    - Mah-Mil, 1936-1970 (Folder 23)
    - Mod-Naf, 1936-1970 (Folder 24)
    - National Broadcasting Company-Poole, 1936-1970 (Folder 25)
    - Press-Ruc, 1936-1970 (Folder 26)
    - Say-Smith, 1936-1970 (Folder 27)
    - Smith-Swi, 1936-1970 (Folder 28)
    - Tyl-Zif, 1936-1970 (Folder 29)
    - Misc., 1936-1970 (Folder 30)
  - Finances, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Movies, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 32-43)
    The Public Opinion Quarterly organized its articles into specific sections. Movies was one of those sections. Items in this subseries consist primarily of correspondence about articles that would fall under the movies section of the journal.
    - Abb-Bra, 1936-1970 (Folder 32)
    - Children's Aid Society of New York-Dal, 1936-1970 (Folder 33)
    - Dav-Eas, 1936-1970 (Folder 34)
    - Films For Democracy, 1936-1970 (Folder 35)
    - Films For Democracy, 1936-1970 (Folder 36)
    - Fur-Ive, 1936-1970 (Folder 37)
    - Kamin Publishers-Losey, 1936-1970 (Folder 38)
    - Mac-The National Board of Review of Motion Pictures, 1936-1970 (Folder 39)
    - Oli-Roc, 1936-1970 (Folder 40)
    - Ros-Thr, 1936-1970 (Folder 41)
    - Weh-Works Progress Administration, 1936-1970 (Folder 42)
    - Misc., 1936-1970 (Folder 43)
  - Operations, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Organizations, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Press, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 46-61)
    The Public Opinion Quarterly organized its articles into specific sections. Press was one of those sections. Items in this subseries consist primarily of correspondence about articles that would fall under the press section of the journal.
    - Abb-Ames, 1936-1970 (Folder 46)
    - Atw-Car, 1936-1970 (Folder 47)
    - Contributions, 1936-1970 (Folder 48)
    - Cop-Dab, 1936-1970 (Folder 49)
    - Dav-Dru, 1936-1970 (Folder 50)
    - Emergency Peace Campaign, 1936-1970 (Folder 51)
    - Eth-Gar, 1936-1970 (Folder 52)
    - Gra-Kob, 1936-1970 (Folder 53)
    - Las-Lee, 1936-1970 (Folder 54)
    - Life, 1936-1970 (Folder 55)
    - Mac-Mur, 1936-1970 (Folder 56)
    - Nas-Rob, 1936-1970 (Folder 57)
    - Sar-Sto, 1936-1970 (Folder 58)
    - Swa-Wil, 1936-1970 (Folder 59)
    - Woo-Zif, 1936-1970 (Folder 60)
    - Misc., 1936-1970 (Folder 61)
  - Publications, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Radio, 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 63-83)
    The Public Opinion Quarterly organized its articles into specific sections. Radio was one of those sections. Items in this subseries consist primarily of correspondence about articles that would fall under the radio section of the journal.
    - Bal-Bur, 1936-1970 (Folder 63)
    - Bur-Cel, 1936-1970 (Folder 64)
    - Chu-Dod, 1936-1970 (Folder 65)
    - Educational, 1936-1970 (Folder 66)
    - Eng-Het, 1936-1970 (Folder 67)
    - Hog-Kir, 1936-1970 (Folder 68)
    - Kirc-Lan, 1936-1970 (Folder 69)
    - Mah-Mck, 1936-1970 (Folder 70)
    - Mey-Mil, 1936-1970 (Folder 71)
    - Mor-Pey, 1936-1970 (Folder 72)
    - Pay-Poole, 1936-1970 (Folder 73)
    - Poole-Pra, 1936-1970 (Folder 74)
    - Radio v. Press, 1936-1970 (Folder 75)
    - Ram-Say, 1936-1970 (Folder 76)
    - Schr-Slo, 1936-1970 (Folder 77)
    - Spi-Str, 1936-1970 (Folder 78)
    - Str-Tuc, 1936-1970 (Folder 79)
    - Wea-Wol, 1936-1970 (Folder 80)
    - Misc., 1936 (Folder 81)
    - Misc., 1937 (Folder 82)
    - Misc., 1936-1970 (Folder 83)
  - Misc., 1936-1970 (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Southern Interscholastic Press Association (SIPA), 1937-1991; 2.5 Linear Feet (Box 1-6, Folder 1-117)